Indiana University President's Office records, 1996-2003 C269
Indiana University Archives
Indiana University President's Office records
1996-2003
Jan.-June 2003
Indiana University Archives
Indiana University. President
C269
13 cubic feet
The first president of what was then Indiana College was elected by the Board of Trustees in 1829. Gerald L. Bepko served as interim president of Indiana University January through July 2003. Collection consists of one series, Subject files, and is comprised of records collected and created by Bepko and his office during his six month tenure as interim president of Indiana University. A wide range of topics are covered in the records, including IU athletics, the regional campuses, and Bepko's files on the I-69 controversy.
Access Restrictions
Select files closed to researchers. These are indicated in the finding aid.
Advance notice is required for access.
Biographical Note
Gerald L. Bepko was born in Chicago, Illinois, on 21 April 1940 to Geraldine F. and Lewis Bepko. Bepko was a bright student and was entered into a program called "Double Promotion" which enabled him to skip a grade during his grade school career. He graduated in 1957 from Carl Scherz High School, a co-educational institution. Bepko's father passed away in 1958, and his mother remarried in 1961.
After having spent his formative years on the North side of Chicago where he excelled as a student, he decided to enroll at Northern Illinois University where he graduated with a B.S. in 1962. He was the first member of his family to graduate from college. Eligible for the draft and unsure of what he wanted to do, he was convinced by a family friend and member of the Board of Kent College of Law in Chicago to apply for entrance into the school. He did and was accepted into the law program where he earned a J.D. in 1965.
Still eligible for the draft after graduation but protected by a deferment, Bepko felt the need to serve his country in some capacity. He applied to the United States Navy Judge Advocate General Corps (JAG), the United States Army Officer Candidate School, and the Federal Bureau of Investigations (FBI). The FBI was particularly alluring to him due to the new found popularity of Ian Fleming's James Bond series. He heard first from the F.B.I. and became an agent in 1965.
During his time as an agent Bepko was involved in a very serious accident that almost cost him his life. Just married to Jean Cougnenc in February 1968, Bepko was assigned to a surveillance mission in New York City. In September of that same year the truck he was in was struck by another car, and he was thrown from the vehicle. The truck then tipped over landing on top of Bepko almost crushing him to death. Shortly after this incident, Bepko resigned from the F.B.I in 1969 and turned to teaching, which would become his life-long career.
Almost five years after his graduation from Kent College of Law, Bepko returned to Chicago to teach. He served at the school from 1969-1971. Having decided to go back to school to earn his L.L.M., Bepko applied for and was appointed the Ford Urban Law Fellow at Yale University in 1971. When he resigned his position at Kent College he had been appointed as the Director of the Institute for Criminal Justice. He received his L.L.M degree from Yale in 1972.
Bepko joined the Indiana University faculty at the School of Law-Indianapolis in 1972, becoming a full professor in 1975, associate dean for academic affairs in 1979, and dean of the law school in 1981. He has been a visiting professor at the University of Illinois, Ohio State University and Indiana University Bloomington
At the time of his appointment to Interim President of Indiana University, Bepko was serving as Chancellor of Indiana University-Purdue University at Indianapolis (IUPUI), a position which he had held since 1986. He served as interim president from January-July 2003, when the university officially appointed Adam Herbert as president in August 2003.
Bepko is married to Jean B. Cougnenc of New York, and they have two children, Gerald L. Jr. and Arminda.
Arrangement
The collection consists of one series: Subject files.
Scope and Content Note
This collection consists of one series entitled Subject files, which is arranged alphabetically by the original folder title. The Subject files are comprised of the records created and collected by Bepko during his interim presidency and were kept in the original order they were received from the Office of the President. The series ends with Alpha Files, which are copies of official letters sent from the President's Office arranged alphabetically by the surname of the recipient. Topics of interest include but are not limited to visits to the regional campuses of the Indiana University system, IU Athletics, the I-69 controversy, and notes from Indiana University Board of Trustees meetings.
Records of a sensitive or confidential nature have been removed from the files and stored in Box 13. These are labeled as "Restricted file removed" in the folder list. Some folders only have certain records removed from them, which are also stored in Box 13 but retain the same folder title from which they were pulled. These files are labeled as "Restricted records removed."
Separated Material
Duplicates numbering more than three have been removed from the collection.
Acquisition Information
Accessions 2003/075, 2003/141, 2004/001, 2005/011 (materials from Jan.-July 2003)
College presidents --Indiana --Archives.; College presidents --Indiana --Correspondence.; Universities and colleges --Indiana --Administration.; Indiana University -- Administration; Indiana University. President -- Archives; Indiana University. President -- Records and correspondence; Indiana University. President -- History -- 20th century -- Sources; Indiana University. President -- History -- 21st century -- Sources; Bepko, Gerald L. -- Archives; Bepko, Gerald L. -- Correspondence
- Subject files, 1996-2003
  - A, general, March-July 2003 (Box 1)
  - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), Feb.-April 2003 (Box 1)
  - Academic Freedom, March 2003 (Box 1)
  - Accountability, May 2003 (Box 1)
  - Accreditation, Feb.-April 2003 (Box 1)
  - Admission Inquiries, Dec. 2002-July 2003 (Box 1)
    General
    (Restricted file removed)
  - Advanced Research and Technology Institute (ARTI) (Box 1)
    - 2002, undated (Box 1)
    - Jan.-June 2003 (Box 1)
  - Advisory Committee (Box 1)
    - Nov. 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 1)
      (Restricted records removed)
    - March-April 2003 (Box 1)
  - Affirmative Action (Box 1)
    - General, Dec. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 1)
    - University, April-July 2003 (Box 1)
  - African-American History Museum, March 2002-April 2003 (Box 1)
  - African-American Studies, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 1)
  - Alberts, Jeff, March 2003 (Box 1)
  - Alliance Document, Jan. 2003 (Box 1)
  - Alliance for Indiana's Future, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association, Dec. 2002-July 2003 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Executive Council Members, 2002-2003 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Survey Report, Feb. 2003 (Box 1)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, Dec. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 1)
  - American Council of Education (ACE), Jan.-May 2003 (Box 1)
  - Amicus Brief, Jan. 2003-April 2003 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report, ca. Dec. 2002 (Box 1)
  - Art Museum, June 2003 (Box 1)
  - Articulation and Transfer, Feb.-April 2003 (Box 1)
  - Articles, Feb.-June 2003 (Box 1)
  - Arts and Humanities, Feb.-March 2003 (Box 1)
  - Arts and Humanities Task Force, June 2003; undated (Box 1)
  - Arts Week, Nov. 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 1)
  - Associations (Box 1)
    - General, Feb.-July 2003 (Box 1)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU) (Box 1)
      - Jan.-July 2003 (Box 1)
      - Spring Meeting, April 2003 (Box 1)
    - American Association of State Colleges and Universities (AASCU), Jan.-April 2003 (Box 1)
    - American Association of Higher Education (AAHE), May 2003 (Box 1)
    - Association of Governing Boards (AGB), Jan.-April 2003 (Box 1)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land Grants (NASULGC), May-June 2003 (Box 1)
  - Athletics (Box 2)
    - General, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 2)
    - Big Ten (Box 2)
      - General, Jan.-April 2003 (Box 2)
      - Audits, June 2000 (Box 2)
      - Council of Presidents/Chancellors (Box 2)
        - General, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 2)
        - Agenda and Minutes, June 2003 (Box 2)
        - Expansion Background Material, May 2003 (Box 2)
      - Rules Violations, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 2)
    - CHAMPS/Life Skills & SAAC, undated (Box 2)
    - Compliance Audits, 1996-2002 (Box 2)
    - Compliance Manual, ca. 1998 (Box 2)
    - Compliance Program, undated (Box 2)
    - Contracts, undated (Box 2)
    - Director, March-April 2003 (Box 2)
    - Financial Audit, June 2002 (Box 2)
    - Financial Comparisons, 2000-2001 (Box 2)
    - Financial Disclosures, May-June 2003 (Box 2)
    - Financial Statements, March-June 2003 (Box 2)
    - Goals, 2003 (Box 2)
    - Graduation Rates Reports, 2002 (Box 2)
    - Head Coach Evaluations, July, 2003 (Box 2)
    - Marketing Plan, 2003 (Box 2)
    - NCAA (Box 2)
      - General, Jan.-June 2003 (Box 2)
      - Rules Violations, 1993-2003 (Box 2)
    - Outside Income Agreements, May, 2003 (Box 2)
    - Sport-By-Sport Attendance, 2003 (Box 2)
    - Student-Athlete Support Services, undated (Box 2)
    - Title IX, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 2)
    - Varsity Club (Box 2)
      - General (Box 2)
        - Nov. 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 2)
        - March-July 2003 (Box 2)
      - Board Book (Box 2)
        - Feb. 2003 (Box 2)
        - May 2003 (Box 2)
  - Audiology, Feb.-April 2003 (Box 2)
  - Audits, March 2003 (Box 2)
  - Awards, Jan.-April 2003 (Box 2)
  - B, general, Jan.-Jul 2003 (Box 2)
  - Banta, Trudy, Jan.-March 2003 (Box 2)
  - Barden, Dennis, Nov. 2002 (Box 2)
  - Basketball, Dec. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 2)
  - Bauer, Pat, Dec. 2002-May 2003 (Box 2)
  - Beckley, Ken, April 2002-June 2003 (Box 2)
  - Belsky, Martin, Dec. 2002 (Box 2)
  - Berggoetz, Barb, Jan.-March 2003 (Box 2)
  - Bergland, Bruce, June 2002-June 2003 (Box 2)
  - Betley, Katie, June 2003 (Box 2)
  - BFC Agenda Committee, Feb. 2003 (Box 2)
  - Biology – Molecular and Cellular, March 2003 (Box 3)
  - Biomedical Engineering, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 3)
  - Biotechnology Research and Training Center, Jan.-April 2003 (Box 3)
  - Bippen, Paul, Dec. 2002-April 2003 (Box 3)
  - Black Caucus, March-April 2003 (Box 3)
  - Black Expo, Feb.-March 2003 (Box 3)
  - Bloomington, Nov. 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 3)
  - Bloomington Campus, March-May 2003 (Box 3)
  - Bloomington Commencement Speaker Committee, July 2003 (Box 3)
  - Bloomington Economic Development Council (BEDC) (Box 3)
    - General, Nov. 2002-May 2003 (Box 3)
    - Washington Trip, Feb.-March 2003 (Box 3)
  - Bloomington Faculty Council (BFC), Nov. 2002 (Box 3)
  - Bloomington Mission and Values Statement, undated (Box 3)
  - Books for Life Foundation, July 2003 (Box 3)
  - Borkowski, Chris, April 2003 (Box 3)
  - Borst, Larry, Jan.-June 2003 (Box 3)
  - Boshkoff, Doug, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Boy Scouts (Box 3)
    - General, June-July 2003 (Box 3)
    - Valley Trails BSA Leadership Luncheon, May-July 2003; undated (Box 3)
  - Brater, Craig (Box 3)
    - General, Jan.-June 2003 (Box 3)
    - Presentation, undated (Box 3)
  - Breaux, Billie, April-May 2003 (Box 3)
  - Brehm Provost, Dec. 2002 (Box 3)
  - Brehm/Plater, April 2003 (Box 3)
  - Brenner, Mark, Nov. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 3)
  - Broome, Marion, March-April 2003 (Box 3)
  - Bryson, Mark, Feb. 2003 (Box 3)
  - Budget (Box 3)
    - 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 3)
    - March 2003 (Box 3)
    - April 2003-May 2003 (Box 3)
  - Budget Discussions, March-May 2003 (Box 3)
  - Budget Hearing, Dec. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 3)
  - Budget Office (Box 3)
    - Jan.-March 2003 (Box 3)
    - May-July 2003 (Box 3)
  - Budget Presentation Prep., Dec. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 3)
  - Bursar, Feb. 2003 (Box 3)
  - Burton, Dan, July 21, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Business, School of, Jan-May 2003 (Box 3)
  - Buyer, Steve, July 2003 (Box 3)
  - C, general, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 3)
  - Cambridge, Barbara, Jan. 2003 (Box 3)
  - Canal Study, March 2003 (Box 3)
  - Cancer Center Fund Raising, Jan. 2003 (Box 3)
  - Carroll, Linda, Oct. 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 3)
  - Carroll, Mike, Golf Outing, April 2003-May 2003 (Box 3)
  - Carson, Julia, Jan. 2003-July 2003 (Box 3)
  - Cate, Fred, Nov. 2002 (Box 3)
  - Cedar Crest, undated (Box 3)
  - Center for Young Children, March-April 2003 (Box 3)
  - Center on Congress (Hamilton-Lugar), April-June 2003 (Box 3)
  - Center on Philanthropy, Jan. 2003-May 2003 (Box 3)
  - Center on Urban Policy, Jan. 2003 (Box 3)
  - Centers and Institutes, April-May 2003 (Box 3)
  - Central Indiana Corporate Partnership (CICP) (Box 3)
    - General, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 3)
    - Copy 2, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 3)
    - Board, Nov. 2002-May 2003 (Box 3)
  - Centralization/Decentralization, Feb. 2003 (Box 3)
  - Chairs and Professorships, July 2002 (Box 3)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 3)
    - Indiana, April 2003 (Box 3)
    - Indianapolis, Jan.-March 2003 (Box 3)
  - Chancellor Emeritus – Ken Gros Louis, July 2003 (Box 3)
  - Chancellor Search – IUPUI, Dec. 2001-Feb. 2003 (Box 3)
  - Chancellors, General, April-July 2003 (Box 3)
  - Chancellors' Meetings, Jan.-May 2003 (Box 3)
  - Chancellors' Reviews, April 2003-May 2003 (Box 3)
  - Change of Address, Dec. 2002 (Box 3)
  - Chemistry, March 2003 (Box 3)
  - Chicago-Kent Commencement, March-May 2003 (Box 3)
  - Chocola, Chris, July 2003 (Box 3)
  - Citizens Gas, Dec. 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 3)
  - Civic Engagement, Oct. 2002 (Box 3)
  - Clapacs, Terry (Box 3)
    - Dec. 2002-March 2003 (Box 4)
    - April-June 2003 (Box 4)
  - Clarian/Clarian Board, April 2003 (Box 4)
  - Clarian – Dan Evans, May-June 2003 (Box 4)
  - Clerkin, Tom, 2003 (Box 4)
  - Clowes Charitable Foundation, Feb. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Clubs, July 2003 (Box 4)
  - Cochran, William, Dec. 2002 (Box 4)
  - Cole, Bruce, Dec. 2002-May 2003 (Box 4)
  - College Board, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 4)
  - College Preparatory Initiative, Jan. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Collens, Lew, Nov. 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Columbus Learning Center, Feb. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Commencement 2003, April-May 2003 (Box 4)
  - Commencement Remarks, April-May 2003 (Box 4)
  - Commitment to Excellence (Box 4)
    - March-April 2003 (Box 4)
    - May 2003 (Box 4)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC), Feb.-May 2003 (Box 4)
  - Community College Agreement, May 2001 (Box 4)
  - Compact (Box 4)
    - Campus, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 4)
    - Indiana, June 2003 (Box 4)
  - Complaints, Jan.-May 2003 (Box 4)
  - Computation/Information Building, Dec. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Conflict of Interest Policy, Jan.-April 2003 (Box 4)
  - Congratulatory Letters, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 4)
  - Conner Prairie, June 2003 (Box 4)
  - Consultants for IUF, Feb. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Continuing Studies, Jan.-June 2003 (Box 4)
    Includes Multimedia CD entitled "Technology, Training and Distance Learning"
  - Cook, Bill, March-May 2003 (Box 4)
  - Council on Competitiveness, March-April 2003 (Box 4)
  - Crawford, Bill, Nov. 2002-April 2003 (Box 4)
  - Cronin, Blaise, Jan. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Crows Nest, Indiana, Jan. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Crum, Susan, Feb. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Cyclotron, June 2003 (Box 4)
  - Cyclotron/Proton Therapy/Biomedical, June 2003 (Box 4)
    Includes Proteomics
  - D, general, Jan.-Jul 2003 (Box 4)
  - Dalphin, John, March 2003 (Box 4)
  - Dalton, Dan, Jan.-May 2003 (Box 4)
  - D'Amico, Carol, May 2003 (Box 4)
  - Daniels (Doug) Portrait, June 2003 (Box 4)
  - Dean of Faculties (Box 4)
    - General, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 4)
    - Lunch, March 2003 (Box 4)
  - Dean of Students, Jan. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Dedication of Isthmus and 10th Anniversary, June 2003 (Box 4)
  - Deferred Compensation, March 2003 (Box 4)
  - Dismissal of Tenured Faculty, March 2003 (Box 4)
  - Distinguished Alumni Service Awards (DASA), Jan.-July 2003 (Box 4)
  - Distinguished Professors, Oct. 2002-April 2003 (Box 4)
  - Distributed Education, April 2003 (Box 4)
  - Diversity, Jan. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Drug Prevention, July 2003 (Box 4)
  - Dunn, Mike, Dec. 2002 (Box 4)
  - Dunn, Oscar, Feb.-April 2003 (Box 4)
  - Dunning, Jeremy, April-June 2003 (Box 4)
  - E, general, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 4)
  - Economic Development, March 2003 (Box 4)
  - Economic Development Initiative, Nov. 2002-May 2003 (Box 4)
  - Education, School of, Jan.-June 2003 (Box 4)
  - Education, U.S. Dept. of, Jan., July 2003 (Box 4)
  - Eickmeier, Valerie, March-June 2003 (Box 4)
  - Emergency Planning, March 2003 (Box 4)
    See also: Disaster Planning
  - Emerging Technology Center (ETC) (Box 4)
    - General, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 4)
    - Brochures, June 2003 (Box 4)
    - Dedication, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 4)
  - Energize Indiana Document, undated (Box 4)
  - Energy, U.S. Dept. of, June 2003 (Box 4)
  - Engleman, Ellen, Feb-May 2003 (Box 4)
  - Eno, Bob, Nov. 2002-June 2003 (Box 4)
  - Enrollment, Feb.-June 2003 (Box 4)
  - Environmental Policy, May 2003 (Box 4)
  - Executive Compensation, March-April 2003 (Box 4)
  - F, general, Feb.-June 2003 (Box 4)
  - Facts at a Glance, April 2003 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Colloquium on Excellence in Teaching (FACET), March-May 2003 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Council, Bloomington, Feb. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Council (Box 4)
    - Bloomington, Feb. 2003 (Box 4)
    - University, April-July 2003 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Departures, Jan. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Salaries, April 2003 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Teas, March-April 2003 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Trustee Bill, Feb. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Family Friendly Policy, Feb. 2003 (Box 4)
  - FASE Mentoring Program, March-May 2003 (Box 4)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), Jan., May 2003 (Box 4)
  - Federal Relations, April-May 2003 (Box 4)
  - Financial Aid Report, Official, June 2003; undated (Box 4)
  - 18/20 Financing Committee, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Fisher, Mary, Feb.-June 2003 (Box 4)
  - Florida, Richard, Jan.-Feb. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Food Service-IUPUI, Dec. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Ford, David, Dec. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Foundation, IU (Box 5)
    - Nov.-Dec. 2002, undated (Box 5)
    - Jan.-March 2003 (Box 5)
    - March-May 2003 (Box 5)
    - May-July 2003 (Box 5)
  - Foundations, general, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 5)
  - Founder's Day, Jan.-March 2003 (Box 5)
  - Frapwell, Dottie, Nov. 2002-June 2003 (Box 5)
  - Frederick, Paul, March-April 2003 (Box 5)
  - Frisby, David, Feb. 12, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Froehlich, Jan, Feb. 2003 (Box 5)
  - Fulton, David, Jan.-May 2003 (Box 5)
  - Future Farmers of America (FFA), June 2003 (Box 5)
  - G, general, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 5)
  - Gallahue, David, Feb. 2003 (Box 5)
  - Garrison, Doug, July 2002-March 2003 (Box 5)
    Computer disk in file
  - Garton, Bob, May 6, 2003 (Box 5)
  - George, Tony, Jan.-Feb. 2003 (Box 5)
  - Gill, Jack, Nov. 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 5)
  - Glass, Fred, May 2003 (Box 5)
  - Golf, April-June 2003 (Box 5)
  - Gonso, Harry, June-July 2003 (Box 5)
  - Gonzalez, Gerardo, Dec. 2002-May 2003 (Box 5)
  - Goodrich, Dave, Dec. 2002-June 2003 (Box 5)
  - Goodrich, Dave (Box 5)
    - Federal, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 5)
    - Richard Lugar, May-July 2003 (Box 5)
    - State (Box 5)
      - Jan.-March 2003 (Box 5)
      - April-June 2003 (Box 5)
  - Governor's Budget Recommendations, Jan. 2003 (Box 5)
  - Great Cities' Universities, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 5)
  - Gress, Robin, Dec. 2002-June 2003 (Box 5)
  - Grossman, Elizabeth, Jan.-Feb. 2003 (Box 5)
  - Grudzinski, Przemyslaw, April 2003 (Box 5)
  - H, general, Jan.-May 2003 (Box 5)
  - Hamilton, Lee, Feb.-June 2003 (Box 5)
  - Hardwick, Phil, Feb.-June 2003 (Box 5)
  - Harrison, Bob, Jan. 10, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Hassell, John, April-May 2003 (Box 5)
  - Health Care, Jan.-March 2003 (Box 5)
  - Health Care Resolution, Feb. 2003 (Box 5)
  - Health Information Administration, Feb.-April 2003 (Box 5)
  - Health Insurance, April 2003 (Box 5)
  - Health, Physical Education, and Recreation (HPER), Feb., July 2003 (Box 5)
  - HEC Documents-Long Range Plan, undated (Box 5)
  - Hegarty, Harv, April-May 2003 (Box 5)
  - Heim, Steve, May 2003 (Box 5)
  - Herbert, Thomas, June 2003 (Box 5)
  - Herrell, Ronald - Representative, Jan.-April 2003 (Box 5)
  - Herron, Aug. 2002-May 2003 (Box 5)
  - HESA Brown Bag Seminar, Feb.-March 2003 (Box 5)
  - Hesburgh, Award, March 2003 (Box 5)
  - Hill, Baron, July 2003 (Box 5)
  - Hill, Reuben, April 2003 (Box 5)
  - Hine Medal, Jan. 2003 (Box 5)
  - HIPPA (Health Insurance Probability and Accountability Act), April 2003 (Box 5)
  - Homepages, April 2003 (Box 5)
  - Honorary Degrees (Box 5)
    - General, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 5)
    - Nominations and Correspondence, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 5)
    - Summary Sheets and Biographical Information, Jan. 2003 (Box 5)
      - B-L (Box 5)
      - M-W (Box 5)
  - Hoosiers for Higher Education, Nov. 2002-April 2003 (Box 5)
  - Hossler, Don, Jan.-May 2003 (Box 5)
  - Hostettler, John, July 2003 (Box 5)
  - House Republican Economic Revitalization Plan, April 2003 (Box 5)
  - House Ways and Means Committee, Jan. 2003 (Box 5)
  - Housing at Regional Campuses (Trustee Reports), April-June 2003 (Box 5)
  - Hudson, Herman, Feb.-April 2003 (Box 5)
  - Hunt, Bill, Jan.-May 2003 (Box 5)
  - Hunter, Ron, Jan.-April 2003 (Box 5)
  - Hunt/Walda, Dec. 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 5)
  - Huntsman, Jeffrey, Feb.-March 2003 (Box 5)
  - I, general, Jan.-June 2003 (Box 6)
  - I-69 Conflict, Nov. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 6)
  - I-Light, undated (Box 6)
  - Independent Colleges, March 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana 21st Century Coalition, March 2003 (Box 6)
  - The Indiana Academy, June 2, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Business/Higher Education Forum, March-April 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Business Research Center, Nov. 2002 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Campus Compact, Feb.-June 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Chamber of Commerce Summit for Indiana's Future, Dec. 2002-April 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Commission for Higher Education (Box 6)
    - General (Box 6)
      - Jan.-Feb. 2003 (Box 6)
      - March 2003 (Box 6)
      - April 2003 (Box 6)
      - May 2003 (Box 6)
      - June-July 2003 (Box 6)
    - Budget Presentation, Nov.-Dec. 2002 (Box 6)
    - Conference for University Trustees, Nov. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 6)
    - Recommendations, Dec. 2002 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Conference of Higher Education, March-June 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Daily Student (IDS), Jan.-April 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Department of Commerce, Dec. 2002 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Education Insight, Jan. 13, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Education Policy Center, Feb. 2001 (Box 6)
  - Indiana's Future Fund, Dec. 2002-April 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana General Assembly, Jan.-April 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Genomics Initiative (INGEN), Dec. 2002-June 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Health Industry Forum (IHIF), Jan.-May 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Humanities Council, Feb.-March 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Internet, April 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Lawmakers Roundtable, March 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Legislative Insight, Jan.-April 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Manufacturers Association, Feb. 18, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Memorial Union (IMU), Jan. 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Policy Review, Jan. 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana Proteomics Consortium, Jan.-May 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana State University, Jan. 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indiana University (Box 6)
    - Coke Contract Extension, Revenue/Pricing Impact, undated (Box 6)
    - Essential to Indiana's New Economy, Nov.-Dec. 2002 (Box 6)
    - Fact Book, 2002-2003 (Box 6)
    - President E-mails, Nov. 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 6)
    - Presidential Search, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 6)
    - 2003-2005 Capital Appropriation Request, 2002 (Box 6)
    - 2003-2005 Operating Appropriation Request, undated (Box 6)
  - Indiana Venture Center, March-June 2003 (Box 6)
  - IUPUI (Box 6)
    - General, May 2003 (Box 6)
    - Staff Council, Oct.-Nov. 2002 (Box 6)
  - Indianapolis, April-July 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indianapolis Business Journal, Feb. 2003 (Box 6)